<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<html>
 <body>
  <materias>
   <materia>
    <id>
     33951343
    </id>
    <urgenc>
    </urgenc>
    <copyright>
    </copyright>
    <fornecedor>
    </fornecedor>
    <servico>
    </servico>
    <editoria>
    </editoria>
    <data>
     17/04/2020
    </data>
    <hora>
     12:53:00
    </hora>
    <formato>
     XML
    </formato>
    <destaque>
    </destaque>
    <titulo>
    </titulo>
    <retranca>
    </retranca>
    <ketwords>
    </ketwords>
    <local>
    </local>
    <autor>
    </autor>
    <sinopse>
    </sinopse>
    <editcodigo>
    </editcodigo>
    <url>
    </url>
    <integra>
     <font face="arial" size="3">
      Uncertainties generated by the new friction of President Jair Bolsonaro with the Mayor, Rodrigo Maia, mainly with regard to the approval of measures, support the search for protection in the foreign exchange market, with reflexes on future interest and stock market. After an optimistic start to the day, when it opened in a fall and marked the day&amp;#39;s minimum price of R $ 5.20, the dollar climbed more than seven cents, intensifying the positive adjustment later in the morning, in parallel with the president&amp;#39;s speech Jair Bolsonaro in the possession of Nelson Teich as Minister of Health. According to professionals, there is fear about the vote on the War Budget, in the second round, in the Senate, as an outcome of the Bolsonaro-Maia conflict, which worsened the climate in Congress. The Senate is already considering rejecting or letting the provisional measure of the Green Yellow contract expire. The text was scheduled for this Friday. The report of the text in the House is of the PT, contrary to the measure. Senators cite the short deadline for analyzing the text of a provisional measure. And Mandetta&amp;#39;s departure, it is worth remembering, displeased the congressmen, accompanied by a joint note for the first time from Maia and the president of the Senate, Davi Alcolumbre. A little while ago, it should be noted that the governor of São Paulo, João Doria, disaffected by Bolsonaro, extended the quarantine in the state until May 10. While investors are looking for protection, the Central Bank enters the market, offering new money early in the afternoon, via foreign exchange swap contracts, which slightly slows the price. The fact is that the outflow of foreign investors persists. The troubled political scenario has also imposed itself on the future interest market, and rates are rising, amid technical adjustments. The levels, however, are below those recorded a week ago. On the stock exchange, the change of minister in Health is also not well regarded at a time when the country is looking for ways to mitigate the effects of the disease. The gains are limited by the fall of Petrobras shares, amid evaluations on the presentation of the state company earlier this afternoon and operations related to the expiration of stock options on Monday. The signal remains positive and may allow the second weekly closing in the blue. But it is fragile, even due to the loss of pace in New York. Even so, the shares advance on Wall Street, supported by the combination of hopes of advancing in the treatment of the covid-19, schedule for the reopening of the United States economy and a lower than expected drop in China&amp;#39;s GDP in the first quarter.
     </font>
     <br/>
     <ul>
      <li>
       <font face="arial" size="2">
        EXCHANGE
       </font>
      </li>
      <li>
       <font face="arial" size="2">
        INTEREST
       </font>
      </li>
      <li>
       <font face="arial" size="2">
        HANDBAG
       </font>
      </li>
      <li>
       <font face="arial" size="2">
        INTERNATIONAL MARKETS
       </font>
      </li>
     </ul>
     <br/>
     <font color="#336699" face="arial" size="2">
      EXCHANGE
     </font>
     <br/>
     <font face="arial" size="3">
      The dollar strengthens against the real, after opening lower, due to the uncertainty with the political-fiscal framework of Brazil. In addition to the increase in defensive positions in the exchange rate for the fifth consecutive day, the outflow of foreign investors from the country also persists. There were successive maximums in the spot market of up to R $ 5.2756, up 0.36%, after the speech by President Jair Bolsonaro in the office of Nelson Teich as Minister of Health. That was when the BC announced a new auction of US $ 500 million in foreign exchange swap, which was sold in its entirety and helped to decelerate only the dollar in sight. The manager of Treviso Corretora, Reginaldo Galhardo, says that despite the optimism abroad, there is unease with the domestic political and fiscal scenario. &amp;quot;The fights of President Jair Bolsonaro with the President of the Chamber, Rodrigo Maia, and the Governor of São Paulo, João Doria, and the change of Health Minister raise caution with Brazil and the investor reinforces defensive positions in the dollar and there are new ones capital outflows &amp;quot;, he says. Galhardo says that the concern about the fiscal gap of the states has increased, which worsens the prospects with the primary federal deficit, because of the social isolation adopted by most of the states and that deteriorates the collection of the federation&amp;#39;s entities. Vanei Nagen, from Terra Investimentos, identified at that time that there were fears about voting for the second round of the &amp;quot;war budget&amp;quot;, scheduled for today in the Senate, because of the escalation of the fight between Bolsonaro and Maia. &amp;quot;The fear is about the budget war, if it will incorporate the loss of revenue from the states with social isolation and allow an increase in the debt of the States, with the transfer of the hole to the Union, this could break the accounts of the federal government &amp;quot;, says Nagen. The political dispute raises that risk, he notes. Weak liquidity helps to stretch the high. Only after that, the BC called the new sale auction of $ 500 million in foreign exchange swap, which only caused the dollar in sight to slow the rise. Elson Gusmão, exchange analyst at Ourominas , says that &amp;quot;the political uncertainty we are experiencing is weighing more, for the time being, with the repeated attacks by the President of the Republic on the President of the Chamber.&amp;quot; A lot of political uncertainty overlapping the continuity of the good external mood &amp;quot;, he evaluates. Another factor that drives the dollar against the real, while abroad the signals are mixed against other emerging currencies, it is the question of whether the new Minister of Health, Nelson Teich, will maintain a technical based action in the fight against the new coronavirus or will yield to the pressure of Bolsonaro, added Nagen, from Terra Investimentos. &amp;quot;Bolsonaro was clear yesterday when he said that he will do everything to end social isolation because of the recessive impact on the economy, although the STF has already decided that the president has no power. to do it &amp;quot;, he commented. Nagen&amp;#39;s perception is that the Congressional agenda can keep moving, despite Bolsonaro&amp;#39;s new attacks on the mayor, Rodrigo Maia. Recently, the governor of São Paulo, João Dória, announced the extension of the quarantine until May 10. For Jefferson Rugik, director-superintendent of Correpaerti, investors and the market work with a protective bias due to the new friction between President Bolsonaro and the mayor, Rodrigo Maia. &amp;quot;It is not a time to create conflicts, but to think about the Brazilian people and the recovery of our economy&amp;quot;, evaluates the executive. In addition, he says that foreign investors are also leaving the country and the banks&amp;#39; spread remains high in spot and future currency exchanges. In the spot market, at 12:30 pm, the dollar decelerated the rise, to R $ 5.2566 (+ 0.02%). At the same time, the future dollar for May continued to rise, to R $ 5.2620 (+ 0.45%), with a registered financial turnover of US $ 6.872 billion. In the period, this contract had a minimum of R $ 5.2115 and a maximum of R $ 5.280 (+0.79%). (Silvana Rocha - silvana.rocha@estadao.com)
     </font>
     <br/>
     <a href="#inicio">
      Volta
     </a>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <font color="#336699" face="arial" size="2">
      INTEREST
     </font>
     <br/>
     <font face="arial" size="3">
      The worsening of the political scenario after attacks by President Jair Bolsonaro on the mayor, Rodrigo Maia (DEM-RJ), caused interest rates to invert the signal and start to rise this morning. Operators also point to a technical adjustment movement, since rates are at much lower levels than those seen at the close of Thursday, with a drop of around 50 basis points from the DI to January 2025 . &amp;quot;I believe that they rise due to the fear of the new Bolsonaro x Maia round that may strengthen the governors and, in this case, the Senate approve the anti-Mansueto plan&amp;quot;, evaluates José Faria Junior, managing partner of Wagner Investimentos. maxims also during Bolsonaro&amp;#39;s speech in possession of Nelson Teich as new Minister of Health. Despite the escalation in the number of deaths and contaminated by covid-19 in Brazil, the president said this morning that he asked the Minister of Justice, Sérgio Moro, who gradually reopens Brazil&amp;#39;s borders. He also questioned the decision of the Supreme Court to grant autonomy to governors and mayors to decree social isolation in the face of the pandemic. Another disaffection of Bolsonaro, the governor of São Paulo, João Doria, recently announced the extension of the quarantine until May 10 in the entire state and capital. &amp;quot;We do not take irresponsible measures in São Paulo. We act according to what science determines,&amp;quot; he said. He also said that he sympathizes with Maia and all the parliamentarians who voted to give resources to the states. The Senate, in response to Bolsonaro, considers rejecting or letting the provisional measure of the Green Yellow contract expire. The text was scheduled for today and will expire if it is not approved by the senators until Monday, 20. Behind the scenes, the reasons given would be Bolsonaro&amp;#39;s comments against Congress and the dismissal of Luiz Henrique Mandetta from the Ministry of Health. creates a program to encourage job creation among young people. The government has called for the vote to take place on Monday. The willingness of leaders, however, is to let the measure lapse. At 12:33 pm, the interbank deposit rate (DI) for January 2021 was 3.10%, from 3.05% in yesterday&amp;#39;s adjustment. The DI for January 2023 was 4.72%, of 4.61%, while the maturity for January 2025 was 6.22%, of 6.12%. (Luciana Antonello Xavier - luciana.xavier@estadao.com)
     </font>
     <br/>
     <b>
      12:51
     </b>
     <table bgcolor="#808080" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0">
      <tr>
       <td>
        <table border="0" cellpadding="2" cellspacing="1">
         <tr>
          <td align="center" bgcolor="#91BBEB" valign="top">
           <font color="#FFFFFF" face="verdana" size="2">
            Operation
           </font>
          </td>
          <td align="center" bgcolor="#91BBEB" valign="top">
           <font color="#FFFFFF" face="verdana" size="2">
            Last
           </font>
          </td>
         </tr>
         <tr>
          <td bgcolor="#EBEBEB" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            Fixed-rate CDB 31 days (% pa)
           </font>
          </td>
          <td align="right" bgcolor="#ffffff" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            3.45
           </font>
          </td>
         </tr>
         <tr>
          <td bgcolor="#EBEBEB" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            Working Capital (% pa)
           </font>
          </td>
          <td align="right" bgcolor="#ffffff" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            7.02
           </font>
          </td>
         </tr>
         <tr>
          <td bgcolor="#EBEBEB" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            Hot Money (% am)
           </font>
          </td>
          <td align="right" bgcolor="#ffffff" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            0.82
           </font>
          </td>
         </tr>
         <tr>
          <td bgcolor="#EBEBEB" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            CDI Over (% aa)
           </font>
          </td>
          <td align="right" bgcolor="#ffffff" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            3.65
           </font>
          </td>
         </tr>
         <tr>
          <td bgcolor="#EBEBEB" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            Over Selic (% aa)
           </font>
          </td>
          <td align="right" bgcolor="#ffffff" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            3.65
           </font>
          </td>
         </tr>
        </table>
       </td>
      </tr>
     </table>
     <font>
     </font>
     <br/>
     <a href="#inicio">
      Volta
     </a>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <font color="#336699" face="arial" size="2">
      HANDBAG
     </font>
     <br/>
     <font face="arial" size="3">
      The Ibovespa signal today is positive, which may allow the second weekly close with gains. Despite the recovery, instability is present, which has been a practice especially in this time of crisis caused by the new coronavirus. In addition to the cooling of US stocks, the local situation also does not give rise to optimism, according to respondents. The imbroglio in domestic politics between the Executive and Legislative reinforces the distrust of investors, who already have difficulty in measuring the impact of the pandemic on asset prices, as well as on the economy, with many uncertainties about the future. In addition, the change in the Minister for Health is also not well regarded at a time when the country is looking for ways to mitigate the effects of the disease. Even so, the Ibovespa has risen since the beginning of business, packed by the news - even yesterday - that the US is beginning to prepare to resume activities in some states after social isolation. Information that a new drug against the disease would be successful also reinforces optimism, which is also supported by a less intense drop (-6.8%) than expected (-8.3%) for the Gross Domestic Product (GDP) ) Chinese in the first quarter. This performance supports the shares of mining and steel companies at B3, as Brazil is one of China&amp;#39;s main trading partners. Vale ON and Usiminas PNA, for example, advanced more than 2% close to 12:30 pm, while Gerdau had gains of almost 6%. At 12:39 pm, the Ibovespa rose 0.90%, at 78,515.92 points, after being traded between the minimum of 77,817.46 points and the maximum of 79,846.43 points, interrupting two consecutive days of decline. The volume traded was R $ 7.72 billion, with a projection to close the day at R $ 21.3 billion. Indications that the crisis caused by the pandemic will come to an end allow the valuation of the stock exchanges, says the chief strategist of Levante Ideias Investments, Rafael Bevilacqua. &amp;quot;The expectation of escalation in some segments of the US economy that intend to open their businesses had already excited yesterday when President Donald Trump gave the information, and continues today. In addition, the cure tests for the disease are advancing and, to complete , the data from China suggest a recovery in V of the country &amp;quot;, he cites. However, the gains are limited by the back-and-forth of Petrobras shares, whose investors estimate the fall of almost 8.5% of oil in New York , in addition to the words of the president of the state-owned company, Roberto Castello Branco. Trying to reassure the market, he said the company is prepared to survive the worst case scenario and that, &amp;quot;despite claims, the company will not fail.&amp;quot; He also said that due to reduced demand in Brazil, oil is being exported. At 12:42 pm, the shares of the state-owned company had mixed signals: decrease of 0.13% (PN) and increase of 0.19% (ON). An operator recalls that the instability of Petrobras&amp;#39; shares today may also be related to an early maturity of stock options on Monday, the eve of a holiday in Brazil (Tiradentes Day). &amp;quot;If abroad it loses strength, here too. In addition to winning, internally there is a political fight that hinders even more and prevents support,&amp;quot; says the source.The chief economist at Veedha Investimentos, Camila Abdelmalack, estimates that political instability raises the distrust of the investor, given the uncertainty that this discomfort can generate in public accounts and companies. In the midst of the pandemic situation, he mentions, the market has been operating without much reference, trying to rest on the positive news that is coming out, such as that the USA intends to resume activities even with the advancement of cases of coronavirus and deaths in some places. &amp;quot;And this means that the volatility should continue. It is without reference, it is looking daily for something to support itself. As it has fallen a lot, many sectors are trying to recover,&amp;quot; he says. Regarding the internal political situation, Camila says that this instability is already getting in the way and can be even more annoying in the future. She recalls that the DEM, party to which former minister Luiz Henrique Mandetta (Health) is affiliated, is also the same as the representatives of the Chamber (Rodrigo Maia) and the Senate (Davi Alcolumbre). &amp;quot;You can create a structural problem ahead, limiting the economy, for companies&amp;quot;, he mentions. Today, the oncologist Nelson Teich took a chance at the Ministry of Health. The announcement of Mandetta&amp;#39;s resignation was made yesterday, when President Jair Bolsonaro took the opportunity to attack Mayor Maia Rodrigo. Then, center, right and left deputies showed solidarity with Maia. (Maria Regina Silva - reginam.silva@estadao.com)
     </font>
     <br/>
     <b>
      12:52
     </b>
     <table bgcolor="#808080" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0">
      <tr>
       <td>
        <table border="0" cellpadding="2" cellspacing="1">
         <tr>
          <td align="center" bgcolor="#91BBEB" valign="top">
           <font color="#FFFFFF" face="verdana" size="2">
            Bovespa Index
           </font>
          </td>
          <td align="center" bgcolor="#91BBEB" valign="top">
           <font color="#FFFFFF" face="verdana" size="2">
            Points
           </font>
          </td>
          <td align="center" bgcolor="#91BBEB" valign="top">
           <font color="#FFFFFF" face="verdana" size="2">
            Var. %
           </font>
          </td>
         </tr>
         <tr>
          <td bgcolor="#EBEBEB" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            Last
           </font>
          </td>
          <td align="right" bgcolor="#ffffff" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            78462.65
           </font>
          </td>
          <td align="right" bgcolor="#ffffff" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            0.83638
           </font>
          </td>
         </tr>
         <tr>
          <td bgcolor="#EBEBEB" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            Maximum
           </font>
          </td>
          <td align="right" bgcolor="#ffffff" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            79846.43
           </font>
          </td>
          <td align="right" bgcolor="#ffffff" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            +2.61
           </font>
          </td>
         </tr>
         <tr>
          <td bgcolor="#EBEBEB" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            Minimum
           </font>
          </td>
          <td align="right" bgcolor="#ffffff" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            77817.46
           </font>
          </td>
          <td align="right" bgcolor="#ffffff" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            +0.01
           </font>
          </td>
         </tr>
         <tr>
          <td bgcolor="#EBEBEB" colspan="2" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            Volume (R $ Billions)
           </font>
          </td>
          <td align="right" bgcolor="#EBEBEB" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            8.00B
           </font>
          </td>
         </tr>
         <tr>
          <td bgcolor="#EBEBEB" colspan="2" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            Volume (US $ Billions)
           </font>
          </td>
          <td align="right" bgcolor="#EBEBEB" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            1.51B
           </font>
          </td>
         </tr>
        </table>
       </td>
      </tr>
     </table>
     <font>
     </font>
     <br/>
     <b>
      12:52
     </b>
     <table bgcolor="#808080" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0">
      <tr>
       <td>
        <table border="0" cellpadding="2" cellspacing="1">
         <tr>
          <td align="center" bgcolor="#91BBEB" valign="top">
           <font color="#FFFFFF" face="verdana" size="2">
            Ind. Bovespa Futuro
           </font>
          </td>
          <td align="center" bgcolor="#91BBEB" valign="top">
           <font color="#FFFFFF" face="verdana" size="2">
            BOVESPA INDEX
           </font>
          </td>
          <td align="center" bgcolor="#91BBEB" valign="top">
           <font color="#FFFFFF" face="verdana" size="2">
            Var. %
           </font>
          </td>
         </tr>
         <tr>
          <td bgcolor="#EBEBEB" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            Last
           </font>
          </td>
          <td align="right" bgcolor="#ffffff" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            78630
           </font>
          </td>
          <td align="right" bgcolor="#ffffff" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            -1.0321
           </font>
          </td>
         </tr>
         <tr>
          <td bgcolor="#EBEBEB" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            Maximum
           </font>
          </td>
          <td align="right" bgcolor="#ffffff" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            81025
           </font>
          </td>
          <td align="right" bgcolor="#ffffff" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            +1.98
           </font>
          </td>
         </tr>
         <tr>
          <td bgcolor="#EBEBEB" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            Minimum
           </font>
          </td>
          <td align="right" bgcolor="#ffffff" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            78330
           </font>
          </td>
          <td align="right" bgcolor="#ffffff" valign="top">
           <font face="verdana" size="2">
            -1.41
           </font>
          </td>
         </tr>
        </table>
       </td>
      </tr>
     </table>
     <font>
     </font>
     <br/>
     <a href="#inicio">
      Volta
     </a>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     <font color="#336699" face="arial" size="2">
      INTERNATIONAL MARKETS
     </font>
     <br/>
     <font face="arial" size="3">
      Advances in treatment studies for Covid-19 have reinforced optimism among market players, who since yesterday have welcomed the plan presented by U.S. President Donald Trump to reopen the local economy. The lower than expected drop in Chinese Gross Domestic Product (GDP) in the first quarter contributed to the positive tone, which was reflected in upward trades on the European and New York stock exchanges, where the Procter &amp;amp; balance sheet was also well received Gamble. Risk appetite, which also pushed down the dollar against rivals, however, was not reflected in the Treasuries market. Investors maintained positions in fixed income, accentuating the fall in interest rates. Oil, on the other hand, did not establish a single direction, with the mismatch of demand and supply expectations still causing volatility. The market was encouraged by the news that a drug developed by the American biotechnology company Gilead Sciences is showing promise in studies for a treatment for the new coronavirus. &amp;quot;The market is looking ahead. A drug can change the outlook for social isolation and reduce concerns about a second wave of contagion,&amp;quot; Marcos De Callis, strategist at Hieron Gestora de Patrimônio e Asset, told Broadcast. And these speculations about the quarantine period have given investors relief in the first part of this Friday&amp;#39;s business, which echoed the press conference of the American president. Trump announced his plan to reopen the U.S. economy last night at the White House. The Republican will begin normalization in May, in three phases, and signaled a retreat by granting governors the right to decide on the end of quarantine in their states. &amp;quot;Even a partial reopening of the economy would greatly ease the pressure on companies and workers, who must still focus on maintaining a safe environment and controlling any further spread of the virus,&amp;quot; comments Lindsey Piegza, chief economist at Stifel. On the activity side, there was some relief with indicators of the Chinese economy released this morning. The Asian country&amp;#39;s GDP even fell by 6.8% in the first quarter - a contraction in growth that hasn&amp;#39;t happened there since 1992 - as a direct consequence of the coronavirus, but the reading was smoother than projected by analysts surveyed by the Wall Street Journal, which was down 8.3%. China&amp;#39;s industrial production, on the other hand, fell 1.1% in March compared to the same month of the previous year, well below expectations of a 7.5% drop. With the facts added, at 12:28 pm Brasília, the Dow Jones index rose 1.29%, the S&amp;amp;P 500 advanced 1.19% and the Nasdaq, 0.24%. In Europe, the London Stock Exchange&amp;#39;s FTSE 100 index closed up 2.82%, Frankfurt&amp;#39;s DAX rose 3.15% and CAC 40 in Paris rose 3.42%. Risk appetite also led the dollar to red against rivals, which at the same time yielded 0.30% at 99.726 points, with the US currency yielding to 107.519 yen, the euro rising to $ 1.0877 and the pound sterling. , at $ 1.2794. The optimistic trend, however, was not reflected in all markets, with two-year T-note interest yielding 0.193% at the above time, and ten-year T-note interest at 0.604%. For Callis, from Hieron, the highs of the stock market do not represent an outflow for fixed income investors, still considered as a good investment in the midst of the uncertain scenario. &amp;quot;The bond market is still not believing in this change in the scenario. The outlook is ahead: low inflation, low growth, low interest. So the long rate is low&amp;quot;, he explains. &amp;quot;The stock market is more optimistic. Perhaps you can say that there is a bubble [in variable income], derived from all this bazooka of stimuli&amp;quot;, he adds, pointing out that sectors of the market are evaluating the news in a different way. In the same vein, the Natwest team says that the Treasuries market continues to look at the &amp;quot;half empty glass&amp;quot;. In addition, the news about the Fed&amp;#39;s actions is on the radar. &amp;quot;We expect a range of measures to compensate for the stress&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;he says. Oil has remained volatile and mixed since the beginning of business, with the WTI contract for June falling 1.76%, to $ 25.09 a barrel. , and Brent for the same month rising 0.83%, to $ 28.15 In addition to the considerations on supply and demand, eyeing the production cuts of the Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries (OPEC) and the impacts of Covid -19 on the activity, operators report impacts on the WTI contract expiration quotes for May, on Tuesday. (Eduardo Gayer - eduardo.gayer@estadao.com)
     </font>
     <br/>
     <a href="#inicio">
      Volta
     </a>
     <br/>
     <br/>
     ]]&gt;
    </integra>
   </materia>
  </materias>
 </body>
</html>